A Guide to the Lilla Richards Collection, 1914-2016 (bulk 1970-2001)
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
The Lilla Richards Collection, 1914-2016 (bulk 1970-2001)
Fairfax County Public Library
MSS 06-97
51 linear feet
The Lilla Richards Collection consists of 51 linear feet and 92 manuscript boxes and spans 1914-2016. The earliest materials cover the development of organizations and institutions in the area of McLean, Langley, Great Falls, Lewinsville, and adjoining areas of northern and northeastern Fairfax County, Virginia.
Richards, Lilla Dunovant McCutchen (1939-2020)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Series 4, Boxes 30-31, contains restricted donation records for the “Save Evans Farm” initiative comprising of photocopied personal checks dating from 1998-2000.
Acquisition Information
In August 2015, Lilla Richards transferred this collection to Merrily Pierce and Paul Kohlenberger, who temporarily deposited it the following month with Fairfax County Public Library’s Virginia Room. It was officially donated by Pierce and Kohlenberger in March 2019.
Historical and Biographical Information
Lilla Dunovant McCutchen Richards was born in Washington, D. C., on March 17, 1939. She was the daughter of James M. McCutchen, an electrical engineer, and Emily Dunovant, natives of South Carolina. Lilla grew up in Arlington County, Virginia, after her family moved there in the early 1940s and was educated in Arlington County Public Schools. She received a B. S. degree from the University of South Carolina. During her childhood, she spent the school year in Northern Virginia and parts of the summers in South Carolina.
Lilla married Stanley I. Richards on July 24, 1965, in Alexandria, Virginia. From 1965-1971, the Richards lived in Tysons Corner, Virginia, and in 1971 moved to nearby McLean. She became involved in civic-association activities while simultaneously working as an editor for the Federal government. Her keen interest in civic affairs lead to her departure from the government position in 1973 and an increasingly deep involvement in local politics.
Richards was involved with the McLean Citizens Association for over 40 years, serving as its president (1977-1978). She served as the second vice president, first vice president, and then president of the Fairfax County Federation of Civic Associations between 1979 and 1982. Richards also served as a member of the National Capital Region Transportation Planning Board.
In 1987, she was elected as a Democrat to serve on the Fairfax County Board of Supervisors as the member for the Dranesville District encompassing McLean, Tysons Corner, Lewinsville, Great Falls, and other communities in northern and northeastern Fairfax County bordering the Potomac River. Her term ended in 1991, but Richards remained active in civic affairs from many years thereafter into the early twenty-first century. She died on September 22, 2020, in Arlington, Virginia.
Scope and Content
The Lilla Richards Collection consists of 51 linear feet and 92 manuscript boxes and spans 1914-2016. The earliest materials cover the development of organizations and institutions in the area of McLean, Langley, Great Falls, Lewinsville, and adjoining areas of northern and northeastern Fairfax County, Virginia. Most of the collection concentrates on the 1970s to the 1990s, however, and focuses on every type of development issue that has challenged the McLean community during a period of rapid and intense population growth. The bulk of this collection consists of correspondence, public documents and reports, maps, newspaper clippings, photographs, newsletters, and other materials relating to the growth and development of the McLean, Virginia, area.
When placed in the library for processing, the collection had been loosely arranged into broad subject areas. During the rearrangement of the papers in the 42 banker boxes, many stray items were found scattered throughout requiring considerable sorting. It should also be noted that some papers from McLean Citizens Association past-presidents Conrad Clark and Theodore Gray were incorporated into the collection when donated. Researchers should note that there were some undated papers in the collection.During the sorting process into chronological order of many sections, undated papers were left with the previous dated document as a general date indicator. Every effort was made to date materials from internal information or context in their original order, but some materials defied assignment of year of creation.
Researchers would do well to search this guide for terms of interest because many topics are scattered throughout the collection and could not be gathered into one location. The collection now maintains a considerable amount of the original order of the materials therein, but many files and papers were relocated to represent specific topics when possible. Any one document could contain multiple subjects, especially government documents and MCA or MCF publications, minutes, and associated papers.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Duplicate and extraneous material.
Index Terms
Buckley, Lynda Van Devanter (1947-2002); Chesterbrook (Va.) - History; Clark, Conrad; Coalition to Save Evans Farm; Dranesville (Va.) - History; Dulles Toll Road; Duval, Clive L., II (1920-); Evans Farm Inn (McLean, Va.) - History; Fairfax County (Va.). Board of Supervisors; Fairfax County (Va.) - Annexation; Fairfax County (Va.) - Civic Associations; Fairfax County (Va.) - Government and Politics; Fairfax County (Va.) - Land use and planning; Fairfax County (Va.) - Roads; Fairfax County (Va.) Board of Supervisors.; Fairfax County Parkway (Va.) - History; Falls Church (Va.) - Annexation; Georgetown Pike; Gray, Theodore L. (1922-2020); Great Falls (Va.) - History; Hazel, John T. (Til) (1930-); Herndon (Va.) - History; Hodges, McCloud B., Jr. (1919-2003); Lambert, Jefferson (Jay) Hamilton (1940-); Langley (Va.) - History; Lewinsville (Va.) - History; McLean (Va.) - Government and Politics; McLean (Va.) - History; McLean (Va.) - Parks; McLean Citizens Association - History; McLean Citizens Foundation - History; McLean Community Center - History; McLean Community Foundation - History; McLean Planning District PLUS Task Force; Milliken, John G. (1945-); Moore, Audrey Campbell (1928-2018); Pimmit Hills (Va.) - History; Potomac View Secondary School (Proposed) (Va.) - History; Richards, Lilla Dunovant McCutchen (1939-); Roads - Virginia - Fairfax County; Shacochis, John (1915-2004); School and Civic League of McLean (Va.); Thoburn, Robert L. (1929-2012); Tysons (Va.) - History; Tysons Corner (Va.) - History; Tysons Corner Center (Tysons I) - History; Tysons Corner Center (Tysons II) - History; United States. Central Intelligence Agency - History; Washington Dulles International Airport; Washington National Airport
Container List
- Series 1: Biographical Files, 1968-2016
  - Lilla Richards Biographical Material [photos], 1970-2016 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Original Box Inventories, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Rubber stamp, "Lilla Richards McLean Archive", Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - McLean Room Proposal for Dolly Madison Library, 1997-2007 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "Edgefield Advertiser", Edgefield, S. C., newspaper [This newspaper is from the county where Lilla Richard's parents originally lived.], 1970; 1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bumper stickers: "Stop the Los Angelization of San Diego" and "You've Obviously Mistaken Me for Somebody Who Gives a Damn", 1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Calendar, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Calendars, 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Calendars, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Calendars, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Calendars, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Calendars, 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Calendar Appointment Book, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Calendar Appointment Book, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Calendar Appointment Book, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Calendar Appointment Book, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Calendar Appointment Book, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Calendars, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Calendar Appointment Book, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 1992 Schedule, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Address Books, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper clippings, Northern Virginia debutants and cotillions, 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Invitation, Dedication of the Alexander Hamilton statute, Treasury Department, Washington, D. C.,, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Caricature of Lilla Richards presented to her by Long & Foster Realtors (oversize), Undated (Drawer OV Drawer)
- Series 2: McLean Citizens Association Administrative and Subject Files, 1914-2010
  - MCA General History and McLean History, 1914-2000 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - MCA Certificates of Incorporation, Supplements, Constitution & Amendments, Correspondence; Reports to the State Corporation Commission, 1923-1965 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - MCA Board of Directors Minutes, 1961-1970 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - MCA General Membership Meeting Minutes, 1957 April 30-1968 October 23 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - MCA Board Members and Civic Association Lists, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - "Five Key Reasons for Consolidation" by Fairfax County Federation of Citizens Associations, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Apartments in McLean, 1960-1962 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Civil Defense Reports, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Fairfax County Pamphlets, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - MCA Financial and Property Documents, 1959-1961 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Proposed Town of Lewinsville, 1962; 1973 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Proposed Pimmit Freeway - Documents and Maps, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - McLean Recreation Council, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - MCA Resolutions, 1955-1961 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - MCA Resolutions etc., 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - McLean Development Committee - Minutes and Papers, 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - MCA Committee for Adjustments to Desegregation; Eugene E. Threadgill recommendations, 1960 November 28 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - MCA Nominating Committee Reports, 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - MCA Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - MCA Awards, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Environmental Advisory Commission, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Parking Lot Regulations, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Article: Land-Use Controls Quarterly (Fall 1969), 21-24. William E. Finley. "Partners in Profit: A Financial Breakthrough for Local Governments.", 1969 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Memo, Ed Mainland to Minerva Andrews regarding "Standards for Drainage Design in Fairfax County, Va.", 1972 April 5 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Amendment to Title 33.1 Code of Virginia (Highways, Bridges, and Ferries…), ca. 1971 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Letters, Streets in McLean, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Letter, Frank Macioge, Architect, to Mrs. Doris Johnson, McLean Planning Committee, Re: McLean Central Area Design Guidelines, 1972 January 17 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - A Guide to Parking Lot Requirements by the County of Los Angeles, Calif. Regional Planning Commission., ca. 1972 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Fairfax County Continuing Review Committee - Standards for Drainage Design, 1972 May (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Booklet "Highlights" Northern Virginia District Conference on Environment & Development, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Bulletin of the Dranesville Environmental Force, Elizabeth Miles Cooke, acting editor, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - MCA Testimony before BOS on Erosion Control, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Notes, "Establish a Board of Environmental Affairs", Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Memorandum, Fairfax County to Developers, subdividers, engineers, and surveyors, 1967, 1969, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Fairfax County Erosion and Sedimentation, 1966, 1969, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence and reports on Roads and Marie Butler Leven Preserve, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Lists of MCA Board members, presidents, committees 1921-2010, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - MCA Certificate of Incorporation as Amended June 1, 1953 and associated papers, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - MCA Deeds (photocopies), 1953-1954 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - MCA Insurance Bond 53 F 2779 with Aetna Casualty and Surety Company (photocopy), 1954 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - MCA Deed, J. Foster Hagan, (relating to the division of the property of John V. Washington) (photocopy), 1955-1957 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - MCA Deed from Eugenia G. Ashby (photocopy), 1957-1958 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - MCA Liability Policy with Aetna Casualty and Surety Company (photocopy), 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - MCA Attorney correspondence and settlement sheet for sale of land to Jack Coopersmith and Esther L. Coopersmith (photocopies), 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - MCA Deed from Albert Segord Anderson and Dorothy L. Anderson, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - MCA Liability Policy with Aetna Casualty and Surety Company (photocopy), 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - MCA Lawsuit against the McLean Lions Club (photocopies), 1951-1955 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - MCA Correspondence, Fact Sheets, and Newspaper Articles, 1963-1966, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - MCA Constitution and Bylaws, 1972-1980 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Maps of the McLean Planning District; Comprehensive Plan McLean Planning District; Area II maps from 1975, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - MCA McLean Planning Committee Minutes, 1972 May-June (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - MCA Newsletters and Committee Report Drafts, ca. 1972? (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - MCA Board of Directors Minutes (1970-1972); General Meeting Minutes (1971, 1972); Annual Meeting Minutes (1971, 1972); Executive Committee (minutes June 24, 1971), 1970-1972 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - MCA Board of Directors and General Membership Resolutions, 1970, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - MCA Board of Directors Minutes (1972-1973); Annual Meeting Minutes (1972-1973), 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - MCA Board of Directors Minutes, 1972 May-July (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - MCA Board of Directors Minutes, MCA Annual Meeting (1973, 1974), 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Handwritten Notes relating to MCA gift of lots for MCC, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - MCA Treasurer Report, 1973 October 24-1974 January 23 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - MCA Board of Directors Minutes, 1974 May 1-September 4 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - MCA Board of Directors Minutes, 1974 October 2-December 23 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - MCA Treasurer Reports, 1974 September; 1975 January 1-May 28 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - MCA Board of Directors Minutes, 1975 January 8-March 5 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - MCA Board of Directors Minutes and Various Committee Minutes, 1975 April 2 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - MCA Transportation Committee Materials, 1973-1989 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - MCA Board of Directors Minutes, 1975 May 7-July 9 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - MCA Board of Directors Minutes, Treasurer's Report Calendar Year 1975. Handwritten "Attendance Record" for MCA Board members 1975-1976. P&Z Committee materials., 1975 August 6-December3 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - MCA Board of Directors Minutes, 1976 January 7-February 4 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - MCA Board of Directors Minutes, Planning and Zoning Committee materials. (Includes "Baptist Church Property" plat map), 1976 March 3-April 28 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Clippings on McLean-related topics, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - MCA McLean Trees Committee Reports and Associated Materials (Includes 1985 Site Plan-Proposed Planting for The Italian Oven, 6852 Old Dominion Drive; Theodore Gray Material), 1972-1986 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - MCA Planning and Zoning Committee Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - MCA Board of Directors Minutes, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - MCA Board of Directors Minutes, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - MCA Nominations for Board of Directors., 1976 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - MCA McLean Spring Festival Flyer, 1975, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - MCA Planning and Zoning Committee Papers (Includes map of Area II Pending Zoning Cases, July 1, 1975), 1975-1977 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - MCA Treasurer's Report (and newspaper clippings), 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - MCA Correspondence and Notes regarding Board Members (Includes a few nomination forms for Board Members.), 1977 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - MCA Board of Directors Minutes, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - MCA Correspondence and Board Nomination Papers, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - MCA Correspondence RE: Subdivision Names, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - MCA Planning and Zoning Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - MCA Material on Proposals to incorporate McLean as a town (Theodore Gray Material), 1978-1983 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - MCA Board of Directors Minutes, 1977 May-1978 April (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - MCA Board of Directors Minutes (Includes Lilla Richard's May 24, 1978 final letter as MCA president), 1978 May-1979 April (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - MCA Membership Lists, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - MCA Legislative Package (material relating to the Virginia General Assembly Session of 1978), 1978 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - MCA Planning and Zoning Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - MCA Control Data Corporation Site (Tysons-McLean Office Center), 1979 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - MCA Board Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - MCA Transportation Committee (Idlewood Road; Spring Hill Road; Great Falls Street; COG Transportation Control Plan), 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - MCA Board Minutes and Agenda (Includes some handwritten notes and meeting notices.), 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - MCA Nominating Committee, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - MCA Board Minutes (includes McLean Fall Festival poster), 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - MCA Board Minutes, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Speech and Notes, "There Is No Such Thing as a Vacant Lot." (Lilla Richards handwritten speech on the history of the MCA and county zoning and planning.), 1981 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - MCA Nominating Committee, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - MCA Letter, Metrorail position to the membership, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - MCA Transportation Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - MCA Planning and Zoning Committee, 1982 January 6 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - MCA Newspaper Articles on Local Topics (Tycon buildings, etc.), 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - MCA Board Minutes and Committee Reports (Includes Christian Embassy issue and sale of Merrimac Estates), 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - MCA Transportation Correspondence and Notes, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - MCA Nominating Committee, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - MCA Budget and Economics Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - MCA Committee Chairs and Members, 1982-1984 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - MCA Correspondence (Theodore Gray Material), 1982-1984 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - MCA Executive Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - MCA Education Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - MCA Environment Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - MCA Fairfax County Annual Plan Review, 1982-1984 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - MCA Board Minutes and Notes. (Also: MCA Committees - Chairs and Members; Public Safety Committee; Candidates Night for elections, 1981-1983), 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - MCA Internal Revenue Service Papers, 1982-1984 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - MCA Treasurer's Manual and Papers, 1977, 1979, 1981-1983 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - MCA Legislative Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - MCA Membership Committee and Membership Lists, 1982-1984 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - MCA Nominating Committee, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - MCA and Other Organizations (Theodore Gray Material), 1982-1984 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - MCA Parks and Recreation Committee (Theodore Gray Material), 1982-1984 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - MCA Publicity (Includes Lewinsville Park Dedication program) (Theodore Gray Material), 1982-1984 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - MCA Public Safety Committee (Theodore Gray Material), 1982-1984 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - MCA Central Intelligence Agency Transportation Issues (Includes a copy of the CIA Environmental Assessment Route 123-Off-Site Road Improvements at the CIA Entrance), 1964, 1984-1988 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - MCA Transportation Committee and Planning and Zoning Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - MCA Fairfax County Secondary Road Construction Program as of October 31, 1984, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - MCA Board Minutes and Attachments, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - MCA Treasurer's Report, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - MCA Planning and Zoning Committee (Includes Tycon Center model photo), 1982-1984 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Brochure for the Colonies Condominium at McLean, Virginia, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - MCA Transportation Committee (Includes 1981 planning report for Chain Bridge Road.), 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - MCA Planning and Zoning Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - MCA Civic Association Lists, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - MCA Membership Lists, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - MCA Board Minutes and Committee Reports (Includes lists of Nominees for MCA Board of Directors 1985-1986, and MCF Board of Trustees, 1985-1988), 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - MCA Newspaper Clippings on Transportation and Planning, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - MCA Newspaper Clippings on Lorton, Virginia Redevelopment, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - MCA Photographs (Include Lilla Richards, Jack Hannon, Bishnu Poudel, Virginia Holton, Dingwall Fleary, Peter Browing, Barbara Browning, Evelyn Swindler, Theodore Gray, Helen Gray, etc.), 1986 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - MCA Newspaper Clippings on 1986 Events, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - MCA Board Minutes, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - MCA Planning and Zoning Committee, 1986-1976 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - MCA Planning and Zoning Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - MCA Transportation Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - MCA Nominating Committee, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - MCA McLean Central Business District Concept Plan, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - MCA Treasurer's Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - MCA Board of Directors Minutes and Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - MCA Nominating Committee, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Clippings on Fairfax County Events and Election, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper Clippings on Fairfax County Events and Growth Issues, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - MCA Board of Directors Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - MCA Planning and Zoning Committee (Budget and Taxation Committee correspondence; Conrad Clark correspondence), 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - MCA Budget and Taxation Committee (Conrad Clark documents), 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - MCA Brochure, ca. 1988 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Clippings on Fairfax County Events and Growth Issues, 1988-1990 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - MCA Board of Directors Minutes, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - MCA Board of Directors Minutes, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - MCA Planning and Zoning Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - MCA Budget and Taxation Committee Papers, 1990 Part 1 (Conrad Clark documents), 1990 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - MCA Budget and Taxation Committee Papers, 1990 Part 2 (Conrad Clark documents), 1990 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - MCA Board of Directors Minutes, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - MCA Planning and Zoning Committee, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - MCA Board of Directors Minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - MCA Lists of Officers of Dranesville District Civic Associations (also, List of Dranesville Commissioners, 1959-1984), 1992-1994 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - MCA Hazel Peterson Tysons-McLean Office Park, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - MCA Nominating Committee, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - MCA Nominating Committee Applications, 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - MCA Board of Directors Minutes, 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - MCA Planning and Zoning Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - MCA Nominating Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - MCA Board of Directors Minutes, 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 5)